[
    {
        "front": "しっぱい（する）",
        "back": "mistake / to make a mistake; failure / to fail",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "このあいだ",
        "back": "recently",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "エレベーター",
        "back": "elevator",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "エスカレーター",
        "back": "escalator",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "いそぐ",
        "back": "to hurry",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふむ",
        "back": "to step on",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "まちがえる",
        "back": "to get (~) wrong",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "しかた",
        "back": "way of doing",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "きづく",
        "back": "to notice",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "あやまる",
        "back": "to apoligize",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "なおす",
        "back": "to repair; to correct",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）なおる",
        "back": "to be repaired; to be corrected",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "そだてる",
        "back": "to grow; to educate",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    },
    {
        "front": "つつむ",
        "back": "to wrap",
        "chapter": "N4 C24"
    }
]
